[{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":28604,"timeElapsed":123119},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":18527,"timeElapsed":141647},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":14455,"timeElapsed":156103},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":22583,"timeElapsed":178687},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":15647,"timeElapsed":194335},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":18454,"timeElapsed":212791},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":10215,"timeElapsed":223008},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5550,"timeElapsed":228560},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":6071,"timeElapsed":234632},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":23734,"timeElapsed":260647},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":18479,"timeElapsed":279127},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":15055,"timeElapsed":294183},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9366,"timeElapsed":303551},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9600,"timeElapsed":313151},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":11150,"timeElapsed":324303},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":11679,"timeElapsed":335983},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7888,"timeElapsed":343871},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5511,"timeElapsed":349383},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":24559,"timeElapsed":375695},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8126,"timeElapsed":383823},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":15495,"timeElapsed":399319},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":12223,"timeElapsed":411543},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":10991,"timeElapsed":422535},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980759769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8863,"timeElapsed":431399},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7655,"timeElapsed":439055},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4207,"timeElapsed":443263},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":13127,"timeElapsed":456391},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":16495,"timeElapsed":474383},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980811849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":483479},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":10735,"timeElapsed":494215},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980835785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":13199,"timeElapsed":507415},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7943,"timeElapsed":515359},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":8039,"timeElapsed":523399},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5198,"timeElapsed":528598},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980860849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3880,"timeElapsed":532479},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7439,"timeElapsed":539919},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":10319,"timeElapsed":551559},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980890385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":10455,"timeElapsed":562015},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":10895,"timeElapsed":572911},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7519,"timeElapsed":580431},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980929329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":20527,"timeElapsed":600959},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3991,"timeElapsed":604951},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980945937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":12615,"timeElapsed":617567},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980957441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11503,"timeElapsed":629071},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980968585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11143,"timeElapsed":640215},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":8335,"timeElapsed":649750},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988473,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10351,"timeElapsed":660103},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6855,"timeElapsed":666959},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":21967,"timeElapsed":688927},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6927,"timeElapsed":695855},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981036465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":12239,"timeElapsed":708095},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981040777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":712407},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981046561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5783,"timeElapsed":718191},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981051017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4455,"timeElapsed":722647},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981054392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":726022},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981074785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":19127,"timeElapsed":746415},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981079377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4590,"timeElapsed":751007},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981089041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":9663,"timeElapsed":760670},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981101912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":12870,"timeElapsed":773542},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981123904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":21992,"timeElapsed":795534},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981130673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6767,"timeElapsed":802302},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981138616,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7943,"timeElapsed":810246},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981144529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5911,"timeElapsed":816159},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981151216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6686,"timeElapsed":822846},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8343,"timeElapsed":831190},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981174976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":14078,"timeElapsed":846606},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981179888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4911,"timeElapsed":851518},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981194672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":14783,"timeElapsed":866302},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981199656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4983,"timeElapsed":871286},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981205576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5919,"timeElapsed":877206},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981210536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4959,"timeElapsed":882166},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981222040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":11503,"timeElapsed":893670},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981228032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5991,"timeElapsed":899662},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981234552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":906182},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981250920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":15087,"timeElapsed":922550},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981255856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4934,"timeElapsed":927486},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981272016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":16159,"timeElapsed":943646},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981285904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":13887,"timeElapsed":957534},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981294848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8943,"timeElapsed":966478},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981299072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4223,"timeElapsed":970702},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981305448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6375,"timeElapsed":977078},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981309088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":980718},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981316880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":7791,"timeElapsed":988510},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981336424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":18623,"timeElapsed":1008054},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981347336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":10911,"timeElapsed":1018966},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981360672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":13335,"timeElapsed":1032302},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981373208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":12535,"timeElapsed":1044838},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981385680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":12471,"timeElapsed":1057310},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981394168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":8487,"timeElapsed":1065798},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981401600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7431,"timeElapsed":1073230},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981407473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5871,"timeElapsed":1079103},{"subjectID":"pyctv1478o","prolificID":"5ee0edcb962eba464f486b40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b27109d34a51975095ed","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981411320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3846,"timeElapsed":1082950}]